mobilekarma.com 2014-06-06

# Privacy Policy

_Last Update: April 10, 2013_

Mobile Karma recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of certain information collected about the users and visitors of our website. This Privacy Policy Statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

By using our website, you signify your agreement to Mobile Karma's Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. Your continued use of Mobile Karma and/or ReCellular-affiliates' websites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**1\. WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

**A. General**

This policy covers how Mobile Karma treats personal information that Mobile Karma collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Mobile Karma products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, job title, employer, or phone and fax numbers, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**B. Companies Not Controlled**

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Mobile Karma does not own or control or to people that Mobile Karma does not employ or manage.

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

**A. General**

**1\. Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** When you visit our site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes pages visited, types of products purchased, and feedback from our visitors, as well as location data, logs and other communication data, and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible. Pages of the site may use devices that permit us to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We may share your PII and non-personal information, including your name, address, email address and any transactions you conduct on our website with us with a third party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver tailored advertising to you that match your interests when you visit our website as well as other websites. Our advertising partner will anonymize the data that we provide so that no one else will receive your PII.

You may opt-out of the use of your information for tailored advertising purposes. To learn more about the use of this information or to choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner by opting out please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by [**clicking here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). _If you delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice._

**2\. Personally Identifiable Information.** Mobile Karma collects personal information when you register with Mobile Karma, when you use Mobile Karma products or services, when you visit Mobile Karma pages or the pages of certain Mobile Karma partners, and when you enter contests, promotions or sweepstakes. Mobile Karma may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

**3\. Information Sought.** When you register we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, member or project ID, password, password hint, job title, company name, address, telephone and fax numbers. Once you register with Mobile Karma and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

**Purchase or Sale of Products or Services Online.** Mobile Karma will collect your contact and payment information (including name, postal address, email address, credit card number, or other financial transaction information).

We also use this information to create/update your account, verify your identity, authorize payments, and to send you a confirmation of your payment. We will share your financial information via a secure Internet connection with our order-processing center for the sole purpose of processing your order or refund.

**4\. Right to refrain from giving information.** You have right to refrain from giving us certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of all of our features. We use the information that you provide for to enhance the service, such as responding to your requests. However, you may not mask your identity by providing false or misleading information. For example, you may not use IP masking to mask your Internet access location, including without limitation, proxy servers, masking software or the like.

**5\. IP Address and Cookies.** Mobile Karma automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Mobile Karma cookie information, and the page you request. Most web browsers have the ability to accept cookies, reject cookies, or to prompt the user before accepting them. The help portion of the toolbar of your browser will tell you how to select the option that suits you best. However, disabling the acceptance of cookies allows you to take full advantage of some of the best and most advanced features that we have to offer, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user will remain anonymous to us.

Mobile Karma may also use technologies such as cookies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of advertising from Mobile Karma, click here.

**6\. Web Beacons.** Mobile Karma may use web beacons to access Mobile Karma cookies inside and outside our network of websites and in connection with Mobile Karma products and services.

**7\. Software.** During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**8\. Online Advertising.** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

To opt out of these ads, please click here

**9\. Use.** Mobile Karma uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, system administration, diagnose problems with our main computers, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**B. Information Sharing and Disclosure**

**1\. Sharing of Personal Information.** Mobile Karma may share the collected personally identifiable information with a sponsor or other third party that may be interested in serving you, or under the following circumstances:

(a) We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Mobile Karma. These companies may use your personal information to help Mobile Karma communicate with you about offers from Mobile Karma and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  
(b) We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
(c) We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Mobile Karma's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; and  
(d) We transfer information about you if Mobile Karma is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Mobile Karma will provide notice before such information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**2\. CHILDREN UNDER AGE 17**

Mobile Karma does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 17. If you are under 17, please do not register for Mobile Karma or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 17 may provide any personal information to or on Mobile Karma. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 17 without verification of parental consent, we will promptly delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 17, please contact us at [mobilekarma@recellular.com](mailto:mobilekarma@recellular.com)

**3\. COOKIES**

A. **Rights Reserved.** Mobile Karma may set and access Mobile Karma cookies on your computer. We may use these cookies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of advertising provided by Mobile Karma, click here. You may occasionally get cookies from our business partners for advertising and other purposes. Mobile Karma and/or Mobile Karma-affiliates do not control these cookies.

You may opt-out of the use of your information for tailored advertising purposes. To learn more about the use of this information or to choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner by opting out please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by [**clicking here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). _If you delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice._

B. **This Policy Not Applicable to Other Companies.** Mobile Karma may let other companies show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Mobile Karma's cookies.

**4\. YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES**

**A. General**

1\. Editing. You can edit your Mobile Karma account information, including your marketing preferences, at any time.   
2\. Mobile Karma Marketing. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Mobile Karma products and services, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your Mobile Karma account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.  
3\. Account Removal. You can delete your Mobile Karma account by contacting [mobilekarma@recellular.com](mailto:mobilekarma@recellular.com)

**5\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

**A. Limited Access to Information.** We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**B. Federal Compliance.** We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

**C. Protection.** As a user of Mobile Karma goods and/or services, you have the responsibility to maintain the secrecy and/or integrity of any passwords assigned to you and to take reasonable measures to ensure that your password is not misused. You must notify Mobile Karma immediately should you suspect that your password secrecy and/or integrity have been compromised.

**6\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

**A. Updates to the Policy.** Mobile Karma may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your Mobile Karma account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**B. Feedback.** If you have questions or suggestions, please complete contact us at:

Mobile Karma  
ATTN: Webmaster  
1194 Oak Valley Drive, Suite 80  
Ann Arbor,  
MI 48108   
U.S.A.   
Tel: (734) 372-3200
